Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers, 1963 - 2016 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Film
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
    - [Man Looking at a Framed Photograph], undated; 311.0088 (Film 311.0088)
    - [Closeup of Smiling Face], undated; 311.0089 (Film 311.0089)
    - [Unidentified B&W Film Reel], undated; ID: 311.0091 (Film 311.0091)
  - Subseries B: Original Containers
    - "Pierre Ganzel's Imitation of Kiss" by Nick Zedd [Black TDK Container], 2001 (Box 19A)
      Original Housing for Media ID: 311.0001
    - "The Bogus Man" [Rockingham County Public Library Metal Container with Gray Plastic Film Reel Holder], 1980 (Box 19A)
      Original Housing for Media ID: 311.0002a - 311.0002b.
    - "Original Nomad" [Eastman Kodak Company Metal Container with Black Plastic Film Reel Holder], undated (Box 19A)
      Media ID: 311.0005, originally found empty with "Nomad" Media ID: 311.0004.
    - "Destination X" [Eastman Kodak Canister], 1976 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0003.
    - "Nomad" [Metal Film Canister], 1978 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0004.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Anthology Film Archives Canister], 1979 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0006.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Eastman/Anthology Film Archives Canister], 1979 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0007a - 311.0007b.
    - "They Eat Scum - Outtakes" [Plastic Canister], 1979 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0008.
    - "They Eat Scum" [Eastman Kodak Canister], 1979 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0009 - 311.0011.
    - "They Eat Scum" [35mm Kodak Canister], 1979 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0012 - 311.0013.
    - "They Eat Scum" [35mm Kodak Canister], 1979 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0014 - 311.0015.
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" [Super 8 Canister], 1983 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0016.
    - "Police State - Fill" [Scotch Magnetic Film Box], 1987 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0026, 311.0028.
    - "Police State - Scene Two Coded Dailies" [White Box], 1987 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0032.
    - "Police Sate Cut Work Pix" [White Box], 1987 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0034 - 311.0035.
    - "Police State - Fill" [White Box], 1987 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0037 - 311.0039.
    - "Police State Dial A & B" [White Box], 1987 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0040 - 311.0041.
    - "Police State" [Anthology Film Archives Metal Canister], 2011 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0447 - 311.0448.
    - "No Title - June 14th 1988" [Du Art Film Box] (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0043.
    - "Whoregasm - Original" [Kin-O-Lux Inc. Box], 1988 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0042, 311.0056.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint for Camera Rolls 3 and 1", 1990s (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0045.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes Kembra" [Metal Precision Film Cannister and Reel], 1990s (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0046.
    - "War Is Menstrual Envy Workprint Positive" [Cardboard Box], 1993 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0047 - 311.0050.
    - "War - Tails Out" [Du Art Film Box], 1993 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0062.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993 (Box 19B)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0063.
    - "War" [Precision Film Laboratories Box], 1990 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0057 - 311.0061.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0064.
    - "War: Credits + Kembra" [Du Art Film Box], 1990 - 1992 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0065.
    - "War: Credits, Kembra + Fish" [Du Art Film Box], 1992 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0066.
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Du Art Film Box], 1993 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0067.
    - "War: World's Fair", 1993 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0068.
    - "Lock, Stock and Barrel" [Blue Film Cannister with Metal Reel], 1995 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0069.
    - "Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative", 1995 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID 311.0070.
    - "1995 Squeezebox" [Du Art Film Box] (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0071.
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Kodak Metal Canister], 1998 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0074 - 311.0075, 311.0077.
    - "Screen Tests" [Du Art Film Box], 1998 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0072.
    - "Screen Tests - B Roll" [Du Art Film Box], 1998 (Box 19C)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0073.
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy" [Kodak Metal Canister], 1999 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0078 - 311.0079.
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Fuji Metal Canister], 2003 (Box 19A)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0080.
    - "Japan" [Gold Metal Cannister and Reel], undated (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0081.
    - "Mixed Misc. Footage" [Brown metal Film Cannister], undated (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0082.
    - "Psycolor" [Paper Box], 1970 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0092.
    - "Harding Productions Inc: Attack of The Giant Fly and Cartoon" [Paper Box], 1968 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0105.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 1" [Metal Canister], 1971 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0106.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 2" [Metal Canister], 1971 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0107.
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible" [Illustrated Metal Canister], 1971 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0108.
    - "Film Epics Volume 1: Harding Productions Inc, Flash Gordon" [Paper Box], 1970 (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0112.
    - "Worm Movie" by Lung Leg [Kodak Paper Box], undated (Box 19E)
      Original housing for Media ID: 311.0132.
  - Subseries C: Juvenilia and Family
    - "Harding Productions Inc: Attack of The Giant Fly and Cartoon", 1968; ID: 311.0105 (Film 311.0105)
      Format: 8mm
    - "Film Epics Volume 1: Harding Productions Inc, Flash Gordon", 1970; ID: 311.0112 (Film 311.0112)
    - "Psycolor", 1970; ID: 311.0092 (Film 311.0092)
    - "Psycolor" [Painted Reel], 1970; ID: 311.0084 (Film 311.0084)
      Format: Handpainted 16mm Clear Reel
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 1", 1971; ID: 311.0106 (Film 311.0106)
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible - Part 2", 1971; ID: 311.0107 (Film 311.0107)
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible" [Illustrated Canister], 1971; ID: 311.0108 (Film 311.0108)
    - "Grimy Underpants: An Atrocity by James Harding", undated; ID: 311.0117 (Film 311.0117)
    - [Harding Family Films], 1956 - 1972 (Box 20, Box 54)
      This is a collection of 21 Harding Family recordings.
      Media ID: 311.0093 - 311.0104, 311.0109 - 311.0111, 311.0113 - 311.0116, 311.000118 - 311.0119.
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - "Worm Movie" by Lung Leg, undated; ID: 311.0132 (Film 311.0132)
    - [Commercial Films], undated (Box 20, Box 54)
      18 commercial films from Zedd's personal collection.
      Media ID: 311.0115 - 311.0116, 311.0118 - 311.0131, 311.0133 - 311.0134
  - Subseries E: Film Documentation
    - Laboratory Forms (Box 19D)
- Series IX: Video recordings
  Series IX: Video includes original moving image elements by Zedd and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
  Subseries B: Acting and Press preserves Zedd's acting work, in addition to interviews and documentaries about the Cinema of Transgression by other filmmakers.
  Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes assorted footage from Zedd's personal video library, rare work by his contemporaries and collaborators, as well as commercial works that Zedd collected.
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
    - "Giant Fly Films", 1968 - 1971; ID: 311.0376 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0376)
      Format: DVD-R
    - "Destination X - A Roll", 1977; ID: 311.0135 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0135)
      Format: VHS
    - "Destination X - A Roll", 1976 - 1977; ID: 311.0454 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0454)
    - "They Eat Scum - Part 1", 1979; ID: 311.0136 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0136)
      Format: U-Matic
      TRT: [01:15:00]
    - "They Eat Scum - Part II", 1979; ID: 311.0137 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0137)
      Format: Sony U-Matic
    - "They Eat Scum - Pt 1 & Pt 2, Bogus Man, Thrust in Me", April 2009; ID: 311.0138 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0138)
      Format: Digital Betacam
      TRT: [01:33:00]
    - "They Eat Scum", 1979; ID: 311.0377 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0377)
    - "The Bogus Man", 1980; ID: 311.0139 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0139)
      Format: MRX UCA-20
    - "The Bogus Man," "Thrust in Me" [Submaster One], 1980; ID: 311.0140 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0140)
      Format: Ampex U-Matic
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Reel One", 1983; ID: 311.0141 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0141)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Part 2", 1983; ID: 311.0142 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0142)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - B&W PAL Master", undated; ID: 311.0143 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0143)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Reel Two Colorlab Transfer", 2002; ID: 311.0144 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0144)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo (Master)", 1983; ID: 311.0145 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0145)
      TRT: [01:10:00]
    - "Geek Maggo Bingo - Photo Gallery", undated; ID: 311.0146 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0146)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Paul Tzenkle Interview with Brenda Bergman, Richard Hell, Donna Death, Nick Zedd", 1983; ID: 311.0147 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0147)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo", 1983; ID: 311.0378 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0378)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch", 1983; ID: 311.0148 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0148)
      Format: Fuji Videocassette
      TRT: [00:28:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch," "Police State," "Whoregasm" [Submaster Tape Two], 1983 - 1988; ID: 311.0149 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0149)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch (Improved Version)," "Bogus Man," " School of Shame (Excerpt)", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0150 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0150)
      Format: Betacam SP
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch and Other Films by Nick Zedd", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0151 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0151)
      TRT: [00:60:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch (Needs Sound)", 1983; ID: 311.0152 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0152)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch, " "Bogus Man" [Unopened Penetration Films Screeners Version], 1980 - 1983; ID: 311.0153 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0153)
      TRT: [00:39:00]
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch - Interview Master", 1980 - 1989; ID: 311.0154 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0154)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch - Master Tape", 1980 - 1984; ID: 311.0155 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0155)
    - "Master - Wild World of Lydia Lunch, Etc.", 1980 - 1989; ID: 311.0156 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0156)
      Contents: "Bogus Man," "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell," "Thrust in Me," "Radio Thin Air Interview with Nick Zedd, Claudia T.V."
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell", 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0157 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0157)
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go To Hell", 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0158 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0158)
    - "King of Sex," "Thrust in Me," "Kiss Me Goodbye," "Go to Hell" (Master Tape), 1984 - 1986; ID: 311.0159 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0159)
    - "Me Minus You", July 12, 1985; ID: 311.0160 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0160)
      Format: Beta Videocassette
    - "Me Minus You Plus 'Dear Cunt' with Zedd, Legere, Pryor", July 12, 1985; ID: 311.0161 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0161)
    - "Wanna Go Out? Richard Hell + Nick Zedd, Blank Generation, Ultra's, Brando in Court", c1987; ID: 311.0374 (Box 21, Media ID: 311.0374)
    - "Police State - Master Tape", June 1, 1994; ID: 311.0162 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0162)
      TRT: [00:18:00]
    - "Twenty Something Program 2 - Reel 2", January 15, 1988; ID: 311.0163 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0163)
      Format: Sony BRS
      Contents: "Police State" and "Whoregasm" by Nick Zedd, "The Cowboy Stories" and "Cornella, Story of a Burning Bush" by Kembra Phaler
    - "Police State - PAL Master", 1987; ID: 311.0164 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0164)
    - "Police State (Old Scratched Master)", 1987; ID: 311.0165 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0165)
    - "Rubric Records 'Police State' ", October 16, 2000; ID: 311.0166 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0166)
      TRT: [00:20:50]
    - "Whoregasm", 1988; ID: 311.0379 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0379)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part 1", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0167 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0167)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part 2", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0168 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0168)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy (CV Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0169 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0169)
      TRT: [01:18:00]
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part One (Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0170 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0170)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part Two (Edited Final Master with End Credits and Ronnettes Music", 1992; ID: 311.0171 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0171)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part II (Master)", 1992; ID: 311.0172 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0172)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Underwater Footage Original)", 1992; ID: 311.0173 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0173)
      Format: Ampex U-Matic SP
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Credits, Underwater Footage, 3/4 in. Unedited No Music - Master)", c1992; ID: 311.0174 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0174)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part III (Opening Credits and Kembra Underwater with Metal Machine Music and End Credits", April 1992; ID: 311.0175 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0175)
      Format: Ampex U-matic
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Part I (Incomplete, Kembra is Missing, Water Footage Gone)", 1992; ID: 311.0176 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0176)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Parts I, II, and III PAL Master", 1990 - 1992; ID: 311.0177 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0177)
      TRT: [01:17:00]
    - "War is Menstrual Envy (Rank Syntel Master)", May 12, 1992; ID: 311.0225 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0225)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy", 1992; ID: 311.0380 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0380)
    - "Screen Tests", January 1998; ID: 311.0187 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0187)
      Format: Sony U-Matic SP
    - "Screen Tests, A.K.A. Why Do You Exist - (Master)", January 1998; ID: 311.0188 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0188)
    - "Why Do You Exist (Master)", 1998; ID: 311.0189 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0189)
    - "Screen Tests (Silent)", c1998; ID: 311.0190 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0190)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants", 1999; ID: 311.0178 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0178)
      TRT: [00:04:30]
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants (Master)", c1999; ID: 311.0179 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0179)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants (PAL Master Without Credits)", 1999; ID: 311.0180 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0180)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants - PAL Original", May 26, 1999; ID: 311.0181 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0181)
    - "Credits: Tom Thumb, Ecstasy in Entropy", undated; ID: 311.0182 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0182)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy and Tom Thumb Credits", undated; ID: 311.0183 (Box 22, Media ID: 311.0183)
      Format: Maxwell KCA - 10BQ
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Unedited HBO Footage of Nick Zedd Shooting with Annie Sprinkle, Brenda Bergman, Will Keenan", November 2, 1998; ID: 311.0184 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0184)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Master Tape", 1999; ID: 311.0185 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0185)
    - "Abnormal: The Sinema of Nick Zedd", c1987; ID: 311.0198 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0198)
    - "Abnormal: The Sinema of Nick Zedd", 2001; ID: 311.0382 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0382)
      Format: DVD
    - "Generation Z: The Movies of Nick Zedd (CV Master)", c1999; ID: 311.0199 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0199)
      TRT: [01:27:00]
    - "Generation Z (PAL)", undated; ID: 311.0200 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0200)
    - "Generation Z: The Movies of Nick Zedd", c1999; ID: 311.0201 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0201)
    - "Rubric Records 'Imitation of Kiss' ", January 29, 2001; ID: 311.0186 (Box 48, Media ID: 311.0186)
      TRT: [00:02:45]
    - "Lord of the Cockrings (Submaster Dub)", 2001; ID: 311.0191 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0191)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings", 2001; ID: 311.0381 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0381)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra (Master)", 2001; ID: 311.0192 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0192)
      Format: Hi8 MP Videocassette
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra (Master)" by Nick Zedd and Jon Vomit, 2001; ID: 311.0193 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0193)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra", c2001; ID: 311.0194 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0194)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra", undated; ID: 311.0226 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0226)
      TRT: [00:45:03]
    - "Elf Panties: The Movie (Master)", 2001; ID: 311.0231 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0231)
      TRT: [00:08:06]
    - "Elf Panties and Lord of the Cockrings", c2001; ID: 311.0230 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0230)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Master)", November 18, 2002; ID: 311.0195 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0195)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation", 2002; ID: 311.0196 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0196)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Master)", 2002; ID: 311.0197 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0197)
      TRT: [00:35:00]
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation (Dub From Beta)", November 19, 2002; ID: 311.0227 (Box 24, Media ID: 311.0227)
    - "Becchky'd Open Mouth Nite (Unedited Master)", 2002 - 2008; ID: 311.0202 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0202)
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008 (Box 24, Box 49, Box 50)
      This is a collection of 45 Electra Elf videocassette masters.
      Media ID: 311.0228 - 311.0229, 311.0233 - 311.0275
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008 (Box 25, Box 50)
      This is a collection of 54 Electra Elf videocassette masters.
      Media ID: 311.0276 - 311.0316, 311.0318 - 311.0319, 311.0321 - 311.0323, 311.0325 - 311.0332
    - [The Adventures of Electra Elf Masters], 2002 - 2008 (Box 26, Box 52, Box 53)
      This is a collection of 8 VHS and 293 Electra Elf Mini DVs.
      Format: VHS, Mini DV
      Media ID: 311.0317, 311.0320, 311.0324, 311.0333 - 311.0337
    - ["The Adventures of Electra Elf" Drafts], 2002 - 2008 (Box 27)
      This is a collection 89 DVD-R and 2 CD-R Electra Elf moving image recordings.
      Format: DVD-R, CD-R
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: The Complete Series", 2010; ID: 311.0385 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0385)
    - "Nick Zedd Video: God Dog", 2007; ID: 311.0445 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0445)
    - "Jake - Designs by Nick Zedd, Monica Casanova", January 16, 2010; ID: 311.0458 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0458)
    - "Microscope Gallery, Nick Zedd Paintings", 2009 - 2011; ID: 311.0457 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0457)
    - "Nick Zedd 2011 Microscope Gallery", ID: 311.0446 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0446)
  - Subseries C: Acting and Press
    - "Cinema of Transgression Volume 1", c1986; ID: 311.0384 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0384)
    - "Cinema of Transgression - NTSC (Incomplete)", c1992; ID: 311.0216 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0216)
    - "Cinema of Transgression - NTSC (Incomplete)", c1992; ID: 311.0215 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0215)
    - "Cinema of Transgression (PAL Master)", c1992; ID: 311.0214 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0214)
    - "History of the Avant-Garde: Cinema of Transgression", 1992; ID: 311.0217 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0217)
      TRT: [02:27:00]
    - "Rage Video Volume II" [copy 1], 1992; ID: 311.0208 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0208)
    - "Rage Video Volume II" [copy 2], 1992; ID: 311.0209 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0209)
    - "Nick Zedd on 'Young Gifted and Broke' ", 1993; ID: 311.0232 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0232)
    - "What About Me" by Rachel Amodeo, November 2, 1993; ID: 311.0212 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0212)
      TRT: [00:12:00]
    - "Bubblegum Footage with Holly Woodlawn, Nick Zedd Interview", 1995; ID: 311.0218 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0218)
    - "Bubblegum" by Peter Strickland, 1996; ID: 311.0210 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0210)
      TRT: [00:15:00]
    - "Joe's Apartment, Previews Starring N. Zedd", 1996; ID: 311.0213 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0213)
    - "Nick Zedd Poetry Project New Year's Day", 1996; ID: 311.0219 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0219)
    - "Chicago Underground Film Festival: Nick Zedd Interview, Press Conference", 1996; ID: 311.0221 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0221)
    - "N. Presley Gershwin Hotel '97: Rebecca, Liz, Andy, Laura, Nick Zedd Projections", 1997; ID: 311.0497 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0497)
    - "Nick Zedd: Footage of Fellini's Basement, Chicago Underground Film Festival", 2000; ID: 311.0203 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0203)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview/Open Mike Part 1+2" by Andreas Troeger, 2001; ID: 311.0223 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0223)
    - "Bulgaria Nightclub NYC: Nick Zedd and Rev Jen Kiss", October 2002; ID: 311.0224 (Box 49, Media ID: 311.0224)
      TRT: [00:06:00]
    - "Interview Nick Zedd, Rev Jen on MNN", 2002; ID: 311.0430 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0430)
    - "Debate with Rev Jen", 2007; ID: 311.0441 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0441)
    - "E.E. + Debate Excerpt", 2007; ID: 311.0455 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0455)
    - "Llik Your Idols", 2007; ID: 311.0383 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0383)
    - "Nick Zedd Speech, Public Access Hearings" Part 1, 2007 - 2008; ID: 311.0468 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0468)
    - "Nick Zedd Speech, Public Access Hearings" Part 2, 2007-2008; 311.0469 (Box 27, Media 311.0469)
    - "Cinema Project Symposium - 4/10", no year; ID: 311.0220 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0220)
    - "Fabulous Disaster/Strange Love" by Scot-Free, undated; ID: 311.0211 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0211)
    - "London Film Festival South Bank Part 1", undated; ID: 311.0204 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0204)
    - "London Film Festival South Bank Part 2", undated; ID: 311.0205 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0205)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview", undated; ID: 311.0222 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0222)
    - "Trailer Trash Night of Shame", undated; ID: 311.0207 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0207)
    - "School of Shame (Incomplete Clone)", undated; ID: 311.0206 (Box 23, Media ID: 311.0206)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - [Assorted Footage 1], various (Box 28, Box 50, Box 51)
      This is a collection of 57 VHS assorted recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Assorted Footage 2], various (Box 29, Box 51, Box 52)
      This is a collection of 55 VHS and 2 Video8 assorted recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Commercial Video 1], various (Box 27)
      This is a collection of 11 DVD commercial recordings from Zedd's personal library.
    - [Commercial Video 2], various (Box 30, Box 51)
      This includes a collection of 39 VHS commercial recordings by Zedd's contemporaries.
    - "The Kinks: The Old Grey Whistle Test X-Mas", 1977; ID: 311.0466 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0466)
    - "Hog Caller Videos, 1 - 7", May 17, 2008; ID: 311.0464 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0464)
    - "The Feminine City" Short Film and Music by Matt Jones, undated; ID: 311.0465 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0465)
    - "NYC - Nov. 02" An Essay Shot by Ludovic DuPrez, 2003; ID: 311.0467 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0467)
    - "Illusion: Travels By Streetcar + Death in the Garden", undated; ID: 311.0470 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0470)
    - "Jared Whitham X-Mass Special Finnel, undated; ID: 311.0459 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0459)
    - "The Jared Whitham Show: Escape New York", undated; ID: 311.0460 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0460)
    - "JWS: 1)Christmas Sandwich, 2)Pizza Future", undated; ID: 311.0461 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0461)
    - "Marc Slanger", undated; ID: 311.0462 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0462)
    - "Rare TV Pilots Volume 1", undated; ID: 311.0463 (Box 27, Media ID: 311.0463)
- Series X: Audio